Okay.
If you're drinking for her today,
you must finish all the alcohol on this table.
Then I won't bother you anymore.
Wishing you both
grow old together.
Okay.
My brother can't drink.
I'll drink for her.
She is my wife.
He drank it all.
Pei Song is so cool!
Song Shiya,
you win.
Pei Song.
Let me tell you,
if you ever dare
treat my Sister Shiya badly,
you'll be answering to
more than just her.
Be careful.
Shiya,
don't go.
Actually,
I have a lot to tell you.
You're drunk today.
Let's talk another day.
No.
It'll be too late if I don't say it now.
There's no time.
Why is there no time?
Is it related to the program you developed?
Pei Song.
Shiya.
Actually, I was reborn.
Trust me,
I will protect you.
My birthday.
I saw in your profile
that your favorite flower is this.
Have you been to all these places?
No.
But
if you want to go,
we can find time to go together.
Have you read all these books?
Basically all of them.
I didn't expect us to have
so much in common.
Shiya,
believe me.
Actually, I was reborn.
I will protect you.
These are the files from Pei Song's computer.
Are you sure that
the big data analysis system he's working on
has a problem?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
From my interactions with him so far,
I don't think he's the kind of person you described.
What kind of person?
The kind who ignores ethics,
and social safety,
a stubborn tech geek who only cares about technological development.
Have you ever heard the saying,
'You can know a person's face, but not their heart'?
We are just taking precautions.
Anyway,
if you find anything,
contact me.
It's almost dawn.
Hurry back.
I'm telling you.
You really need to practice more.
What was that you played today?
It's them who suck.
Damn, who the hell are you?
Are you sick?
I'm your brother-in-law.
Brother-in-law?
When did my sister get married?
Here is a black card.
It has no password.
What does this mean?
Is this for me?
I have only one condition.
Don't participate in any
activities related to big data experiments.
I won't.
Why would I participate in that?
Give me your phone.
Here is my number.
Call me if you need anything.
Okay, brother-in-law.
My sister is doing great.
She found a gold mine.
You're treating us to the internet cafe today.
Shiya,
hello.
How are you feeling today?
I'm not feeling great.
How about you?
I'm doing pretty good.
Why are you in a bad mood?
Because my brother got married.
Don't you dislike your brother
because Grandpa thinks you're not as good as him?
But he is
the only one by my side.
I can stay with you.
I love you.
You are not a real person.
I don't need your love.
I just love you.
Then what do you
love about me?
I love everything.
No,
you have to be specific.
I love all of you.
You have to be more specific.
I love everything.
You can't just say everything.
I want specific traits.
If you can't pick out any, you don't love me.
All of it.
I told you I want specific traits.
I want specific traits.
Features.
All of them.
I need specifics.
Specifics.
All of them.
All.
Hello, Pei Ning.
We've been waiting for you for a long time.